

Dinh Thi Thu Hang

CONTACT INFORMATION

- math display="block" December 19, 1996" in the control of the cont
- Female
- **** 01654256960
- thuhangabc96@gmail.com
- ♥ Hochiminh, Vietnam
- i https://www.facebook.com/hang.thu.191296

OBJECTIVE

Take advantage of IT skills & experience and understanding of computer to find a location at company, where i can be max the IT experience, the organization and the program developmental capabilities. From that, I will contribute to development of Company.

SKILLS

Language English

Slove problem

Team-working

Office sofware

Soft Skills

INTERESTS

I like reading book, listening to music, writing articles, traveling.

EDUCATION

Oct 2014 - Now

Post And Telecommunication Institute Of Technology

Major: Electronic & Electrical Engineering

GPA: 2.6/4

WORK EXPERIENCE

2014 - 2018

PTIT

Senior Student

- Design some simple circuits.
- Find technical document, analyze and suggest the direction of the project
- Science research topic: control smart home on web: Device driver programming on Arduino.
- Be assessed positively by the teacher : active, study and work hard.
- Observe, learn and expand my knowledge.

2015 - 2018

TEACHER

Private teacher

-Tutor for Subjects: Math, Literature, English.

Achievements and skills gained:

- -Ability to improve presentation skills
- Improve English Communication Skill.

2017 - 2018

LG ELECTRONICS COMPANY

Sales

- Sales consultant for electronic products.

Achievements and skills gained:

- -Contact with many partners.
- Improve communication skills.
- Improve English communication skill.

ACTIVITIES

May 2016 - Jan 2018

EDUCATION TALK 2017

Member of Electronic club

- -Post for the programming contest of the club.
- -Share exam skills, pass exams, practice problems.
- -Share how to hunt scholarships and student's life experiences to all students who study at PITT university.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- -I got the scholarship for the 2017-2018 school year.
- -Assistant for design hardware of project: The callhandling system used for the internal model uses Raspberry pi.